[Barking ]
[ Barking ]
[ Clock Chiming ]
나의 이야기는 얼마 전
런던에서 시작된다
My story begins
in London...
not so very long ago.
하도 많은 일이 일어나서
마치 까마득한 옛일 같다
Yet so much has happened since then,
that it seems like an eternity.
그때 난 독신자 아파트에서
애완동물과 살고 있었다
At that time,
I lived with my pet...
- in a bachelor flat
just off Regents Park.
- ♪ ♪ [ Piano ]
때는 독신자에게는 고문이나
다름없는 화창한 봄날이었다
It was a
beautiful spring day,
a tedious time of the year
for bachelors.
Oh... that's my pet,
Roger Radcliff,
저것이 내 애완동물인
음악가 로저 래드클리프다
a musician of sorts.
그리고 나는 바로
점박이 개 퐁고다
I'm the one
with the spots.
My name's Pongo.
As far as I could see,
사람들은 혼자 사는 게
화려하고 자유로운 줄 아는데
the old notion that
a bachelor's life was so...
glamorous and carefree
was all nonsense.
말도 안 되는 소리다
It was downright dull.
얼마나 지겨운 줄 아는가
[ Sigh ]
It was plain to see that
my old pet needed someone.
나의 애완동물도
친구가 필요할 것이다
But if it were left up to Roger,
we'd be bachelors forever.
하지만 로저만 믿고 있다가는
둘 다 총각귀신 될 게 뻔했다
He was married to his work,
writing songs.
로저는 일과 결혼했다
사랑에 대해 하나도 모르면서
Songs about romance...
of all things,
사랑 노래를
작곡한다고 한다
something he knew
absolutely nothing about.
Oh, he's intelligent enough,
as humans go.
로저는 인간치고는
지적인 편이고
And I think you could say, Roger is
a rather handsome animal in his way.
생긴 것도 그런 대로
괜찮은 편이다
I could see no reason
why my pet...
그런데 왜 애인이 없는지
주인인 나도 알 수가 없다
didn't deserve
an attractive mate.
At least I was determined
to do my best.
드디어 내가 나서기로 했다
Of course, dogs are a pretty
poor judge of human beauty.
물론 개와 인간은
미적 기준이 다르지만
But I had
a rough idea...
나도 나름대로
여자 보는 눈은 있다고 확신한다
of what
to look for.
Hmm!
Unusual breed.
상당히 개성 있군
[ Chuckle ]
Very unusual.
아주 특이해
Hmm!
Oh, surely not.
하지만 안되겠어
Well now,
what have we here?
이번에는 또 누군가?
Hmm.
Well, a little...
too short coupled.
못난이 한 쌍이군
Nope!
안되지
I say!
Well, I do say!
저거다!
정말 수준 있는
한 쌍이다!
Now there's
a fancy breed.
Hmm.
Perhaps a little too fancy.
아니, 너무 사치한 것 같아
Yes, much too fancy.
사치하면 안되지
Too old.
Too young.
너무 늙었고
너무 어리고
It was a problem,
a real problem.
쉽지 않은데
Well, now that's
a bit more like it!
이제야 그럴듯한 한 쌍이
나타났군
The most beautiful creature
on four legs!
멍멍이 중에는
최고의 미인이다!
Now if only the girl--
인간 쪽은 어떨까?
Well!
She's very lovely too.
역시 괜찮군!
It was almost too good
to be true.
이건 하늘이 주신 기회야
I'd never find another pair
like that,
백 년을 찾아 헤매도
저런 신부감은 없을걸
not if I looked
for 100 years.
Ah, they're heading
for the park.
공원 쪽으로 가는구나
마침 잘됐다
A perfect meeting place...
if I can only arrange it.
나가자고 해야지
Uh-oh... but Roger never
stopped work 'til after 5:00.
로저는 5시 전에는 절대
자리를 뜨지 않는데
That would be
too late.
그러면 너무 늦어
[ Barking ]
벌써 5시가 넘었네
After 5:00 already.
- Fancy that.
- [ Barking ]
서버렸군
All right, Pongo.
All right, boy.
알았다, 퐁고
[ Barking ]
[ Yipping ]
Pongo, boy,
take it easy!
퐁고, 천천히 가자!
What's all
the hurry?
뭐가 그리 급하니?
[ Barking ]
Pongo, boy,
slow down.
퐁고, 천천히 가
I was afraid we'd missed them.
Perhaps they passed on by the park.
처음에는 놓쳤을까 걱정했다
공원에 들르지 않은 걸까?
Then suddenly...
I spotted them.
순간 그들이
내 눈에 들어왔다
It was a perfect situation
if I planned it right.
계획을 세워도 이보다 더
완벽하진 않을 거다
I couldn't depend on Roger.
I knew what he'd do.
로저만 믿다가는
아무 일도 안될 게 뻔했다
보나마나 잔디에 앉아서
담배만 피울 테니까
He'd settle on the grass, puff
his pipe and that would be it.
No, it was all
up to me.
내가 나서는 수밖에
Well.
At first I had
no particular plan,
처음에는 작전이 스질 않았다
일단 주위를 끌어야 했다
just anything
to attract attention.
다소 소동을
피워서라도 말이다
You know,
stir things up a bit.
Pongo,
you silly old thing!
퐁고, 이 녀석이!
C'mon!
C'mon, let's have it, boy.
왜 이러니, 돌려줘
퐁고!
- Pongo!
- [ Yipping ]
Pongo!
퐁고!
[ Barking ]
[ Pongo ] For awhile,
it seemed to work.
일이 잘되는 듯 싶었다
일단 서로를 쳐다 봤으니까
At least they
had seen one another.
순간 전류가 통하는 듯
했는데...
Things were going along
first-rate.
But for some strange reason
they left!
웬일인지 그냥
자리를 뜨는 것이었다
C'mon, you old renegade.
We're going home.
그만 가자, 퐁고
집에 가야지
[ Pongo ]
But I wasn't giving up.
난 포기할 수 없었다
I was determined that somehow
they just had to meet.
무슨 수를 쓰든 두 사람이
말을 걸게 해야했다
- Oh!
- Ohhh!
I beg your pardon.
Please excuse me.
이런 실례가...
정말 죄송합니다
세상에!
I must say,
what on earth!
하느님 맙소사
- Oh, really. Good heavens.
- Oh, dear.
어쩌면 좋아
- Ohh!
- Ahh, ahh!
Oh, oh.
[ Gasping ]
Oh, my new spring suit
and my new hat!
새로 산 옷인데!
내 새 모자!
[ Roger ] Ah, ah...
I'm terribly sorry.
정말 죄송합니다
Please let me
help you.
제가 도와 드릴게요
죄송해요
I'm so sorry.
저 녀석이 왜 저러는지
모르겠네요
I don't know
what's come over him.
정말 죄송합니다
한 번도 이런 적 없었는데
I'm so sorry. He's never
acted this way before.
됐어요, 괜찮아요
제발 그냥 가주세요
Please, just go away.
You've done enough.
제발요
Please?
Oh.
제 것을 쓰세요
Oh, I say.
Here, take mine.
Oh.
[ Laughing ]
아내를 아끼고 사랑하며
존중할 것이며
Wilt thou love her,
comfort her,
honor and keep her
in sickness and in health;
아플 때나 건강할 때나
늘 지켜주며
머리가 파뿌리 될 때까지
서로 사랑하겠습니까?
and forsaking
all others,
keep thee only unto her
so long as ye both shall live?
사랑하겠습니다
[ Roger ]
I will.
[ Pongo ] For the first
six months or so...
처음 6개월 정도는
공원 근처 작은집에서 살았다
we lived in a small house
near the park,
a modest little place...
두 쌍의 신혼 부부가 살기에
적당한 크기였다
but just right for two couples
who were just starting out.
♪ ♪ [ Piano ]
Perdita, darling,
are you all right?
퍼디, 당신 괜찮아?
[ Chuckle ]
Oh, of course, dear.
그럼요, 여보
새끼를 낳는 거예요
누구나 하는 일인 걸요
After all, dogs were having
puppies long before our time.
[ Chuckle ]
[ Pongo ] Oh, that's Nanny,
a wonderful cook and housekeeper.
저분은 우리 유모다
살림에 요리솜씨가 일품이다
She's such a kind,
understanding soul.
게다가 인정도
얼마나 많은지 모른다
You know,
어떨 때는...
잘 훈련된 경찰견같다
at times she seems
almost canine.
Roger, dear,
여보, 차 드세요
tea time.
Tea time!
어서요!
[ Roger ]
♪ Be down in a minute ♪
♪ Ta tum ti ta tum ♪
♪ Do you like my new song ♪
'새 노래 어때요?'
♪ Ta tum ti ta tum ♪♪
Such clever lyrics.
'랄라라라...'
가사가 좋군요
[ Chuckle ]
Melody first, my dear.
멜로디부터 만들고
가사는 나중에 붙일 거야
And then the lyrics,
hmm?
[ Car Horn ]
Oh, Pongo... it's her.
It's that devil woman.
퐁고, 그 여자예요
그 마녀 같은 여자
[ Car Horn ]
[ Roger ] Oh, must be Cruella, your
dearly devoted old schoolmate.
크루엘라일 거야
당신 동창 말이야
Cruella de Vil.
'크루엘라 드빌'
바로 그거야!
That's it!
♪ Cruella de Vil ♪
'크루엘라 드빌
크루엘라 드빌'
♪ Cruella de Vil ♪
'무서운 여자
너무 두려워'
♪ If she doesn't scare you
no evil thing will ♪
- Oh, Roger.
- ♪ To see her is to take
a sudden chill ♪
'그녀만 보면 소름이 끼쳐'
Ohh!
♪ Cruella... Cruella ♪
'크루엘라
크루엘라'
♪ She's like a spider
waiting for the... kill ♪
'먹이를 기다리는
거미 같은 여자'
Roger,
she'll hear you.
여보, 듣겠어요
♪ Look out for
Cruella de Vil ♪
'크루엘라 드빌'
Let her in, Nanny.
열어드려요, 유모
- Anita, darling!
- How are you?
안녕, 아니타
어서 와
Miserable as usual.
Perfectly wretched!
사는 게 이렇게 지겹고
따분해서야!
Where are they?
어디 있어?
어디 있는 거야?
For heaven sakes,
where are they?
도대체 어디 있어?
- Who, Cruella?
- The puppies! The puppies.
누구 말이야?
강아지들!
No time for games.
Where are the little brutes?
숨길 생각하지 마
새끼는 낳았겠지?
♪♪ [ Trumpet ]
적어도 3주는 있어야 해
서두른다고 될 일이 아니야
It'll be at least three weeks.
No rushing these things.
[ Chuckle ]
Anita, you're such a wit.
귀여운 아니타
언제나 말을 잘하지
Here, dog, here.
이리와, 멍멍아
- Here, dog.
- [ Growling ]
Cruella, isn't that
a new fur coat?
크루엘라
그거 새로 산 모피니?
My only true love,
darling.
내 삶의 유일한 기쁨이지
I live for furs.
I worship furs!
난 모피 없으면 못 살아
모피가 너무 좋아
Is there a woman in this
wretched world who doesn't?
여자치고 모피 싫어하는
여자 있으면 나와보라고 해
Oh, I'd like a nice fur,
but there are many other thing--
모피도 좋지만
그밖에도 좋은 게 얼마든지...
Sweet, simple Anita.
[ Chuckle ]
순진하긴
I know, I know!
그래 알아듣겠다
This horrid little house
is your dream castle.
네게는 이 작은 집이
꿈의 궁전 같겠지
And poor Roger is your
bold and fearless Sir Galahad!
가난한 로저는
널 지켜주는 기사일 테고
Oh, Cruella.
크루엘라
Then of course you have
your little spotted friends.
게다가 점박이 친구들까지
있으니
Oh yes,
정말 아름다운 코트가
될 거야
I must say... such perfectly
beautiful coats.
- Won't you have some tea?
- I've got to run.
차 한 잔 할 테야?
아니, 가봐야 해
새끼 낳는 대로 연락해 줘
Let me know when
the puppies arrive.
- You will, won't you, dear?
- Yes, Cruella.
-꼭이야, 알았지?
-알았어
잊지마, 약속했어
그럼 3주 후에 봐
Don't forget, it's a promise.
See you in three weeks.
잘 있어
Cheerio, darling.
Ohh!
♪ At first you think
Cruella is a devil ♪
'처음에는 그 여자
악마인 줄 알았지'
♪ But after time
has worn away the shock ♪
'충격을 가라앉히고
생각해 보니'
♪ You come
to realize ♪
'그 눈빛 어디선가
본 듯 했어'
♪ You've seen
her kind of eyes ♪
♪ Watching you from
underneath a rock ♪
'그건 바로
동굴에 붙어있는 박쥐'
- You're no help.
- ♪ This vampire bat ♪
그만해요
'인간의 가면을 쓴
흡혈귀 같은 여자
♪ This inhuman beast ♪
영원히 가둬서
풀어주지 말아야 해'
♪ She ought to be locked up
and never released ♪
♪ The world was such
a wholesome place until ♪
'크루엘라 드빌이 오기 전에는'
♪ Cruella ♪
'온 세상이 평화로웠지'
♪ Cruella de Vil ♪ ♪
Roger,
you are an idiot!
엉뚱한 소리 말아요
[ Laughter ]
- Perdy?
- That witch. That devil woman.
퍼디?
그 여자는 악마예요
She wants our puppies.
That's all she's after.
우리 애들을 노려요
뺏어갈 거라구요
Don't worry, Perdy.
They're on to her.
걱정하지 마, 퍼디
그럴 리 없어
- Nothing's going to happen
to our puppies.
- What does she want with them?
우리 애들에게는
아무 일도 없을 거야
개를 좋아하지도 않으면서
대체 왜 그러는 거죠?
She can't possibly
love them.
Oh, Pongo.
처음에는 아기를 가진 게
너무 행복했는데 지금은...
I was so happy at first,
but now l--
[ Crying ]
Oh, l--
차라리 없었으면 하고
생각해요
I wish we weren't
having any.
[ Thunder ]
[ Pongo ] Poor Perdita.
Of course, she had no choice.
가엾은 퍼디
그러나 어쩌랴
The puppies arrived
right on schedule...
새끼들은 예정대로 비바람
몰아치는 10월에 태어났다
one wild and stormy night
in October.
[ Footsteps ]
Ohh!
Steady, boy.
침착해
[ Nanny ]
The puppies are here!
새끼를 낳았어요
Oh... the puppies
are here!
새끼를 낳았다구요
H-H-How many?
몇 마리죠?
- Eight.
- Eight?
8마리요
8마리?
[ Barking ]
By George, Pongo!
Eight puppies.
세상에, 퐁고
8마리래
Ten.
10마리
- [ Anita ] Eleven.
- Eleven.
11마리!
Eleven?
Eleven puppies, Pongo.
11마리래!
퐁고, 대단하다
Wait a minute now,
wait a minute... thirteen!
잠깐만요, 잠깐만
13마리예요
No, no, no.
Fourteen.
아뇨, 14...
- Ohh... fifteen!
- Fifteen?
15마리예요
15마리나!
And the mother's
doing fine, love.
어미도 건강해요
You ducky thing, you.
기특한 것 같으니
Fifteen puppies?
15마리!
Why, Pongo,
that's marvelous!
퐁고, 정말 대단하다
It's fabulous!
경사로구나
재주도 좋구나, 퐁고
Why, you old rascal!
Fourteen.
14마리예요
Just fourteen.
14마리밖에 안돼요
We lost one.
한 마리가 죽었어요
Poor little thing.
불쌍한 것 같으니
Oh, Pongo, boy.
퐁고야
It's just one
of those things.
이런 일은 있기 마련이야
And yet?
하지만...
And yet I wonder.
어쩌면 말이다...
[ Thunder ]
Look, Pongo.
봐라, 퐁고
Anita!
아니타
Nanny.
Fifteen!
유모!
15마리야, 15마리라구!
We still have
fifteen!
Oh, Roger, he's all right!
Thank heaven.
살아났군요!
고맙기도 해라
See? He's just
as good as new.
봐, 아주 건강하잖아
Can you imagine, Roger,
fifteen puppies!
믿어져요?
15마리래요!
Fifteen.
Fifteen puppies!
새끼를 15마리나?
정말 잘됐어
How marvelous.
아주 좋았어
How marvelous,
how perfectly... ugh!
The devil take it.
They're mongrels... no spots!
어떻게 된 거야?
잡종이잖아? 점이 없네
점이 하나도 없어
하얀 쥐새끼 같아
No spots at all.
What a horrid little white rat.
잡종이 아니에요
곧 무늬가 생길 거예요
They're not mongrels!
They'll get their spots.
Just wait and see.
두고 보세요!
That's right. They'll have
their spots in a few weeks.
맞아, 크루엘라
몇 주 후면 점이 생길 거야
Oh, well, in that case I'll
take them all. The whole litter.
그렇다면 내가 전부 사겠어
통째로 다 말야
Just name your price, dear.
얼마 주면 될까?
I'm afraid
we can't give them up.
미안하지만 그렇게는 못해
어미가 얼마나 상심하겠어
- Poor Perdita, she'd be heartbroken.
- Anita, don't be ridiculous.
아니타, 저것들을 다
어떻게 기르겠다는 거니?
You can't afford to keep them.
You can scarcely feed yourselves.
입에 풀칠하기도
빠듯한데 말야
I'm sure
we'll get along.
어떻게든 살 수 있을 거야
[ Chuckle ]
Yes, I know. I know!
그래, 로저가 작곡해서
말이겠지!
Roger's...
Roger's songs!
[ Laughing ]
Enough of this nonsense. I'll pay you
twice what they're worth.
말도 안 되는 소리 그만해
내가 값을 두 배로 쳐줄게
I'm being
more than generous.
특별히 인심쓰는 거야
Blast this pen.
이놈의 펜이?
이놈의 펜이 왜이래?
Blast this wretched,
wretched pen!
When can the puppies
leave their mother?
언제쯤 어미를 떨어질까?
Two weeks?
Three weeks?
2주, 3주?
[ Roger ] Never.
안됩니다
뭐요?
- What?
- We're n-n-not selling the puppies.
우리는 한 마리도 팔지
않겠어요
Not a single one.
Do you understand?
단 한 마리도
아시겠소?
Anita, is he serious?
아니타, 진짜야?
로저는 이해할 수가 없어
I really
don't know Roger.
- Cruella, he--
- Surely he must be joking!
크루엘라, 로저 말은...
그래, 농담이겠지
진담입니다
한 마리도 줄 수 없어요
No, no, no.
I-l-I mean it.
You're not getting one.
N-N-Not one.
절대로 안됩니다
And that's... final.
얘기는 끝난거요
Why, you horrid man!
웬 잘난 척이야!
You... you...
당신들...
그래! 강아지와 잘 살아봐요
마음대로 해보라구
All right, keep the little
beasts for all I care.
Do as you like with them.
Drown them!
But I warn you, Anita,
I'm through with all of you!
그리고 아니타, 너와는 절교야
다시는 아는 척도 마
I'll get even.
Just wait.
복수하고 말 테다
후회하게 될걸, 멍청이들!
You'll be sorry,
you fools!
You... you idiots!
멍청이들!
[ Door Slams ]
[ Barking ]
여보, 당신 너무 멋있었어요!
Oh, Roger!
You were magnificent, darling.
멋있는 정도가 아니라
영웅이세요, 우리의 영웅!
He was a bloomin' hero,
ma'am!
Indeed he was.
A bloomin' hero!
Perdy?
Perdy, darling?
안심해, 여보
We're keeping the puppies,
every single one of them.
애들을 기를 수 있게 됐어
전부 다 말야
My ol' pet Roger, he told
that devil woman off.
믿음직한 나의 로저가
그 마녀를 내쫓았다구
He told her off, Perdy.
She's gone.
이제 갔어
다시는 오지 않을 거야
- Darling, she's gone for good.
- Oh, Pongo.
퐁고...
- C'mon, Thunderbolt.
-달려라, 번개!
Go get him, Thunder.
어서 잡아, 번개야
After him, boy.
쫓아가!
저 나쁜 말 도둑을
잡아야해
He'll get that
dirty ol' horse thief.
Old ThunderboIt's the greatest
dog in the whole world.
번개는 세상에서 제일
훌륭한 개일 거야
He's even better
than Dad.
아빠보다도 멋있어
No dog's better
than Dad.
아빠보다 멋있는 개는 없어
What's he going to do,
Dad?
번개가 어떻게 할까요, 아빠?
Shh, shh.
Let's just wait and see.
어떻게 하나 보자꾸나
[ Puppy ] Look at him run,
the old coward.
비겁하게
도망치는 것 좀 봐
That old dirty Dawson!
얄미운 도둑놈!
The yellow-livered
old skunk!
간이 부었군!
I'd like to tear
his gizzard out.
깔아뭉개 버려!
[ Perdy ] Why, Patch, where did
you ever hear such talk?
패치, 어디서
그런 말을 배웠니?
Certainly not
from your mother.
엄마는 그런 말 쓰지 않는데
조심해, 번개야!
- Watch out, Thunder.
- Don't worry, Penny.
걱정 마, 페니
저런 간덩이 부은 놈은...
He'll get that
yellow-livered--
Well, he'll get him,
all right.
혼내줄 거야
Lucky, get down.
We can't see.
럭키, 앉아!
안 보이잖아!
Mother,
make him get down.
엄마, 앉으라고 해요
C'mon, Lucky.
Down, dear.
앉아라, 럭키
Missed him.
Missed him by a mile.
빗나갔어!
근처도 못 갔어!
I'm hungry, mother.
I'm hungry.
배고파요, 엄마
배고파요
Rolly, you've just had
your dinner.
방금 저녁 먹었잖니
But I am,
just the same.
그래도 배가 고파요
코끼리라도 먹을 것 같아
I'm so hungry I could eat...
a whole elephant.
Shh!
[ Puppy ] There he is,
behind that rock.
저기 바위 뒤에 있다!
[ Gunshot ]
Oh, dear.
He shot poor Thunder.
번개가 총에 맞았어
He missed him. Ol' Thunder's
pretending... I think.
안 맞았어
죽은 척 하는 걸 거야
[ Wicked Laugh ]
See? What did I tell you?
That's one of his tricks.
내 말이 맞지?
다 속임수라구
럭키, 앉아
- Lucky, get down.
- Ha-ha-ha!
[ Whimpering, Yipping ]
I'm hungry, Mother.
I really am.
배고파 죽겠어요, 엄마
[ TV ] Don't miss next week's episode.
Who will triumph?
다음 주 얘기를 기대하세요
과연 누가 승리할까요?
Ol' Thunder
always wins!
그야 당연히 번개지
And speaking of champions,
friends,
과자의 챔피언은
바둑이 표 비스킷입니다
Kanine Krunchies is the
champion of all dog biscuits.
♪ Kanine Krunchies
can't be beat ♪
'바둑이 표 비스킷은
영양 많고 맛도 좋아'
♪ They make each meal
a special treat ♪
♪ Happy dogs are those who eat
nutritious Kanine Krunchies ♪
'우리들이 즐겨먹는
바둑이 표 비스킷'
여보, 산책 나가려면
애들을 재워야지
Perdy, we better get these
little nippers off to bed...
if we're going for a...
w-a-l-k.
-같이 가고 싶어요, 엄마
-가도 돼요?
- We want to go too, Mother.
- Can we, Mother?
We never
get to go.
우리는 한 번도 간 적
없잖아요
가자, 얘들아
잘 시간이야
Come along, children.
Bedtime.
But we're not a...
[ Yawn ]... bit sleepy.
하나도 졸리지... 않아요
We want to go
for a walk in the park.
우리도 공원에
산책 나가고 싶다구요
- Dad, can we?
- Better do as your mother says.
가도 돼요, 아빠?
엄마 말씀 들어야지
[ Pongo ] One, two,
three, four...
하나, 둘, 셋, 넷...
five, six...
seven...
다섯, 여섯...
일곱,...열 셋
eight, nine, ten, eleven,
twelve, thirteen...
잠은 안 오는데
배는 고파요
I'm not sleepy.
I'm hungry.
fourteen.
열 넷
Hmm?
♪ So do what all
the smart dogs do ♪
'챔피언이 되고 싶은
친구들은 모이세요'
♪ And you'll feel great
the whole day through ♪
'영리한 개들이 즐겨 찾는
바둑이 표 비스킷'
♪ You can be a champion too
if you eat Kanine Krunchies ♪
Remember, friends,
just send five--
잊지 마세요, 여러분
바둑이 표 비스킷은...
럭키야, 너무 늦었다
어서 자야지
Lucky, you little rascal,
let's go.
There they go,
Horace, me lad,
저기 간다, 호레스
언제나처럼 산책을 가는군
out for their
evening constitutional.
A lovely pair
of turtledoves.
한 쌍의 원앙이
따로 없다니까
Around the corner
and off to the park.
저 모퉁이를 돌아
공원으로 가겠지
Yeah, I don't like it,
Jasper.
난 꺼림칙해, 재스퍼
또 걸리면 종신형일거야
One more pinch and
they'll throw the keys away.
Come off it, Horace.
We're getting plenty of boodle.
왜 이래, 호레스
돈이 얼만데 그래!
Yes, but...
I've been thinkin'.
그래도 내 생각에는...
You've been thinkin'?
I warned you about thinkin'.
생각 좋아하네!
생각은 이 형님이 할 테니까
넌 시키는 대로 해
I've got the knob for this job,
so let's get on with it.
Ah, nobody home
but the little ol' cook.
집에는 늙은 가정부 밖에
없을 거야
너는 이 형님의 말솜씨를
구경이나 하란 말이야
You just leave her
to ol' Jasper.
He can handle her
real diplomatic-like.
그래도 난 왠지 싫어
Y eah, but I still
don't like it.
Here, here.
Patch, you settle down.
착하지, 패치
어서 자거라
[ Chuckle ]
Oh, dear.
귀여운 것
눈감고 어서 자야지
Go to sleep now.
Close your little eyes.
That's a good
little one.
귀여운 것들
[ Ringing ]
누구시죠?
Who do you suppose?
Good evening, ma'am.
안녕하십니까
전기회사에서 나왔습니다
We're here to inspect
the wiring and the switches.
가스회사에서 나왔어요
- We're from the gas company.
- Electric, electric.
전기, 전기...
전기회사요
Electric company.
But we didn't call
for any inspection.
신고한 적 없는데요
실은 국회에서 국방에 관한
법이 하나 통과 됐습니다
There's a new act
just been passed in Parliament.
Comes under the heading
of "Defense of the Realm Act."
아주 중요한 거죠, 법이니까요
부인의 안전을 위한 겁니다
It's for your own safety,
ma'am.
법이고 뭐고
들어오게 할 수 없어요
I don't care
whatever it says.
You're not coming in here
with the Mister and Missus gone.
지금은 주인 내외가
집에 안 계세요
Come off it, Ducky.
We got no time to palaver.
실랑이할 시간 없어요
할 일이 많다구요
We got a job to do.
Excuse me!
실례하겠소
What's the matter
with you two?
대체 왜들 이래요?
귀들이 먹었나?
들어오지 말라고 했잖아요
You got cloth ears?
You're not coming in!
She's a regular little tartar,
ain't she, Horace?
이 아줌마 고집이
보통이 아니네
어디를 함부로 올라가요?
키만 멀대 같이 커가지고!
Don't you dare go up there,
you long-legged lummox!
Now I mean it.
If you don't get out
of this house...
당장 나가지 않으면
경찰을 부르겠어!
I'll call the police,
I will.
Now be off with you,
you big weasel!
당장 나가지 못해?
이런 나쁜 사람들!
Now you've been
gone and done it.
얌전하게 말을 들었으면
이런 일은 없잖아
You've cut me
to the quick, lady.
Why, I wouldn't stay here
if you asked me.
내가 있으란 다고 있을
사람인 줄 아나?
차까지 대접하려고?
Not even
for a cup of tea.
Horace, me lad, I've got a sneaky
suspicion we're not welcome here.
호레스, 우리가
못마땅한 모양이야!
Pack up.
We're leaving.
빨리 챙겨서 나가자!
말은 정확히 행동은 빠르게!
Sharp's the word
and quick's the action.
Let me out!
Help!
내보내 줘! 사람 살려!
경찰을 부를 거야!
I'll call the police.
Help!
Good night, Ducky.
Ta-ta!
잘 있어요, 아줌마
Those good-for-nothing
hoodlums!
전기 회사에서
도둑을 키운다더냐?
Electric company.
Hmph!
They're nothing but common
sneak thieves.
좀도둑놈 같으니!
I'll bet they made off
with the good silver.
보나마나 은그릇을
훔쳐 갔을 거야
안 봐도 다 알아
Why, I bet they took
every last--
The puppies!
강아지가 없네!
They're gone!
Patch? Lucky? Rolly?
패치, 럭키, 롤리...
They took
the puppies!
강아지를 데려갔어!
어떡하면 좋지?
Oh...
Whatever will I do?
Those scoundrels!
They stole the puppies.
사기꾼이 강아지를
훔쳐 갔어!
Police? Help!
The puppies.
누구 없어요? 경찰!
누가 좀 도와줘요!
Police!
Somebody help me!
Help! Help! Help!
"Dognapping!"
Can you imagine such a thing?
강아지 납치라
세상에 이런 일이...
'15마리의 강아지를 훔치다'
귀여운 것들
"15 puppies stolen."
They are darling little things.
Anita...
아니타와...
and her bashful Beethoven!
잘난 작곡가 선생
볼만하군!
Pipe and all!
Oh, Roger,
you are a fool!
로저, 넌 바보야
[ Phone Ringing ]
Hello?
여보세요?
재스퍼!
Jasper!
Jasper, you idiot!
지금 제정신이야?
나한테 전화를 하면 어떡해!
- How dare you call here.
- We don't want no more of this,
we want our boodle!
마냥 기다릴 수만은 없잖아요
빨리 수고비 주세요
We'll settle
for half!
반만 받을게요
Not one schilling
'til the job's done.
일이 끝날 때까지는
한푼도 못 줘
Jasper! Jasper!
알아들었나?
신문에 대문짝 만하게
났다구요
It's in the blinkin' papers,
pictures and all!
Hang the papers!
It'll be forgotten tomorrow.
상관없어
내일이면 다들 잊을 텐데
- I don't like it.
- Shut up, you idiot!
난 불안해, 재스퍼
-닥쳐, 멍청아!
-뭐라고?
What?
아닙니다
호레스에게 한 말이에요
Not you, miss.
I mean Horace!
한심한 것들!
Why, you imbecile!
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Roger ]
Maybe it's Scotland Yard.
경시청일거야
단서를 찾았는지도 몰라
Maybe they found something.
Hello, lnspector?
여보세요? 경감님?
-아니타 있어요?
-누구요?
- Is Anita there?
- Who?
아니타요!
- Anita!
- Uh...it's for you.
당신 전화야
Hello?
-아니타, 나야
-크루엘라
[ Cruella ] Anita, darling.
What a dreadful thing.
얼마나 속이 상하겠니
방금 신문에서 봤어
I just saw the papers.
I couldn't believe it.
믿어지질 않아
Yes, Cruella.
It was quite a shock.
그래, 우리도 너무 놀랐어
- Is she calling to confess?
- Roger, please!
왜 전화했대?
자백하려고?
그만해요
교활한 여자 같으니
- She's a sly one.
- We're doing everything possible.
그래
최선을 다하고 있어
- [ Cruella ] Have you
called the police?
- Y es, Scotland Yard.
경찰에는 연락했니?
그럼, 경시청에 신고했어
- But I'm afraid--
- Where are they?
그런데...
어디다 감췄어?
-정신 나갔어요?
-뭐야?
You idiot!
- Anita!
- Sorry, Cruella.
미안해, 크루엘라
소식 있으면 알려줄게
[ Anita ] If there's any news,
we'll let you know.
고마워, 크루엘라
Thank you, Cruella.
크루엘라가 괴팍하긴 해도
도둑질은 안 해요
Roger, I admit she's eccentric,
but she's not a thief.
Well, she's still number one
suspect in my book!
그래도 난 그 여자가
제일 수상해
She's been investigated
by Scotland Yard.
경시청에서 크루엘라를
수사하고 있잖아요
- What more do you want?
- I don't know, darling.
난 모르겠어
정말 모르겠어, 여보
I don't know.
Oh, Roger.
What'll we do?
어떡하죠?
어떡하면 좋아요?
What'll we do?
퍼디, 우리가
나서야 할 것 같아
Perdy, I'm afraid
it's all up to us.
Oh, Pongo.
Isn't there any hope?
아무 희망도 없는 거예요?
Well, yes.
There's the twilight bark.
멍멍이 연락망을 써야겠어
The twilight bark?
That's only a gossip chain.
하지만 그건
비상 연락망이잖아요
Darling, it's the very
fastest way to send news.
소식을 전하는 데는
그게 제일 빨라
아이들이 도시 안에 있다면
런던의 개들이 알 거야
If our puppies are anywhere
in the city, the London dogs will know.
We'll send the word tonight when
our pets take us for a walk in the park.
오늘밤 산책 나갈 때
그 연락망을 이용하자구
[ Barking ]
There's no one out tonight.
I'm afraid it's too cold.
오늘은 아무도 안 나올 거예요
날씨가 너무 추워요
We've got to keep
trying, Perdy.
그래도 시도는 해봐야지
[ Barking ]
[ Distant Barking ]
Perdy,
we're in luck!
퍼디, 운이 좋았어
헴스테드에 사는 대니야
It's the great dane
at Hampstead.
[ Barking ]
퐁고, 조용히 해
Quiet, boy!
자는 사람들을
다 깨울 생각이니?
Do you want to stir up
the whole neighborhood?
- Perdy, come on!
- Let's go.
퍼디, 왜 이러니
가자, 퐁고
- [ Barking ]
- Pongo, you old idiot!
퐁고, 너 왜 이러니?
[ Howling ]
퐁고, 그만 집에 가자!
Come on, now.
We're going home!
[ Pongo Howling ]
[ Barking ]
[ Distant Barking ]
[ Yipping ]
What is it, Danny?
Who's on the telegraph?
뭐야, 대니?
누가 친 전보야?
It's Pongo, Regents Park!
It's an all-dog alert.
리전트 공원에서
퐁고가 보낸 비상 연락이야
뭔데? 내용이 뭐야?
어서 말해 줘, 대니
What's it all about?
Tell me, tell me!
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
잠깐만 기다려
[ Distant Barking ]
이런
Well, now...
Hmm, that is something.
심각한 일이군
What, Danny?
What's something?
뭐가 심각한데?
누가 달마시안 새끼
15마리를 훔쳐갔대
15 dalmatian puppies,
stolen!
Have they called the police?
Scotland Yard?
경찰에는 신고했대?
경시청에는?
The humans tried everything. Now it's
up to us dogs and the twilight bark.
인간이 할 수 있는 건 다 했어
이젠 우리가 나서야 해
멍멍이 연락망 말야
I'll sound the alert!
내가 경보를 울릴게
[ Yipping ]
Woof! Woof!
[ Howling ]
Ahh!
[ Barking ]
프리시, 들어와
Prissy,
come in here!
[ Barking ]
[ Yipping And Howling ]
"애완견 가게"
[ Barking ]
- [ Barking ]
- Coco!
코코, 조용히 해라
Be quiet now!
[ Many Dogs Barking ]
좀 조용히 해!
[ Man ]
Aw, shut up!
시끄러워!
Quiet!
[ Barking Continues ]
Will you be quiet!
조용히 못해!
[ Distant Barking ]
[ Barking ]
[ Howling ]
Towser,
what's going on?
타우저, 무슨 일이야?
무슨 소문이야?
What is it?
What's all the gossip?
'Taint no gossip, Lucy.
It be all the way from London.
소문이 아니야, 루시
런던에서 온 소식이야
- You don't say!
- 15 puppies stolen.
설마!
새끼 15마리를 도둑 맞았대
There's no puppies around here,
not since Nellie's last litter.
이 근처에는
새끼가 없잖아
넬리네 막내도 다 컸는걸
Well, then, we'd best
send the word along.
그럼 다른 지역에
전해 줘야지
대령님께 연락해야 해
It be up to me
to reach the Colonel!
He be the only one
in barking range.
그곳이 가장 가까운
연락망이거든
You'll never reach him
at this hour!
너무 늦은 시간이라
어려울 텐데
Well, I can try!
그래도 해야지
밤새 짖어야 한대도 해야 해
I'll bark all night
if I have to.
Ahem!
[ Barking ]
[ Distant Barking ]
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
Hmm... sounds like
old Towser.
타우저 목소리 같은데?
경보다!
It's an alert.
Sergeant!
상사!
야옹이 상사!
Sergeant Tibs!
I say, Sergeant!
상사!
[ Neighing ]
뭐야?
Oh, yes, Captain!
소대장님이시군요
Barking signal. It's an alert.
Report to the Colonel at once.
당장 대령님께 신호를 보내라
이건 비상 경보야!
Righto, sir.
Right away, sir!
네, 소대장님
당장 연락하겠습니다
Colonel?
대령님!
대령님, 대령님!
I say, Colonel!
Colonel, sir?
- Colonel?
- What? Who goes there?
뭐야, 누가 왔나?
야옹이 상사가 보고 드립니다
Sergeant Tibs
reporting, sir.
야...야...그래, 야옹이 상사로군
Tibs? Tibs?
Oh, yes, Sergeant Tibs!
한밤중에 깨워서
뭘 하라는 거야?
Look here, Tibs. What's the idea
of barging in at this hour?
대령님...
But Colonel--
잠깐, 저 소리 들리나?
- Hold on, Sergeant. You hear that?
- [ Barking ]
비상 경보 같은데?
- Sounds like an alert.
- Y es, Colonel.
맞습니다
무슨 일인가 알아보자
최고 속도로 따라와!
- We'd better look into it.
Come along, on the double.
- Righto, sir.
지금 갑니다
- It's old Towser down
at Withermarsh, sir.
- [ Barking ]
건너 마을의 타우저가
짖는 소리입니다
By Jove, yes!
So it is.
그래, 그렇군
무슨 일인지 물어보자
Well, I'll see
what he wants.
Ahem!
Woof, woof, woof!
It be the Colonel.
The old boy himself!
대령님이 몸소 보내셨군
내용을 말하라는데
He wants the message.
You'd better make it loud
or he'll never get it.
크고 분명하게 전하지 않으면
못 알아들을 거예요
[ Barking ]
One long howl,
two short.
길게 한 번, 짧게 두 번
그리고 으르렁 한 번이라
- One yip and a woof.
- Two yips, sir.
두 번입니다
- What's the word?
- It's from London.
무슨 소식입니까?
런던에서 온 거야
그럼 중요 하겠네요
- It must be important.
- Yes, I'll get the rest of it.
그래, 나머지도 물어보자
Ahem!
Woof, woof, woof!
[ Distant Barking ]
Sounds like a number.
Three fives is 13.
숫자 같은데
3 곱하기 5는 13
- That's 15, sir.
- Of course, 15.
저... 15인데요
15!
그래, 15였지
[ Barking ]
Yes... Dot, Spot--
Spotted puddings.
점... 박이... 점박이
푸들
...
Poodles.
- No, puddles!
- Puddles, sir?
아니, 푸대
푸대요?
15 spotted puddles stolen?
Oh, balderdash!
점박이 푸대 15개를
도둑맞았다는군
- Better double-check it, Colonel.
- [ Grumbling ]
확인해 보는 게 좋겠습니다
대령님
그래, 그러는 게 좋겠어
Oh, yes,
I suppose I'd better.
Woof, woof, woof!
[ Barking ]
깽깽 두 번에
으르렁 한 번이라
Two woofs,
one yip and a woof.
강아지란 뜻 같은데요
- It sounds like "puppies"!
- Of course, puppies!
그래, 강아지였어
I just remembered.
대령님, 이틀 전 유령집에서
강아지 우는 소리를 들었어요
Two nights past, I heard
puppy barking at Hell Hall.
The old de Vil place?
Nonsense, Tibs!
크루엘라의 집 말이냐?
그럴 리가
그 집은 몇 년째 비어있어
No one's lived there
for years.
Hold on! There's smoke
coming from the chimney!
잠깐만요, 그 집 굴뚝에서
연기가 나는데요
[ Colonel ] By Jove, that's strange...
strange indeed.
그것 참 이상하군
정말 이상해
가서 조사해 봐야겠다
I suppose
we'd better investigate.
타우저에게 대기 명령을
내려야지
I'll send word for
ol' Towser to stand by.
Roof! Roo-roo-roof!
Please... stand... by.
대기하라...
그게 무슨 뜻이지?
- What's he mean by that?
- I don't know.
글쎄, 뭔가를 발견하신
모양이지
Oh... maybe the ol' boy's
found something!
Oh, I do hope so.
그랬으면 좋겠다
저 집에는 귀신들이 산다는
소문이 있었는데
They say the ol' place is haunted or
bewitched or some such fiddle faddle.
Fiddle faddle
and rot, sir.
고약한 귀신이래요
Just the same, Sergeant,
use extreme caution.
그게 그거 아닌가
정신 바짝 차려
어떤 귀신을 만나게 될지
아무도 몰라
No telling what sort of
hocus pocus you might run into.
[ Gulps ]
Blast it all, Tibs.
On the double, man.
당장 가서 알아보고 오게
상사, 어서!
- On the double.
- Y es, sir. Right away, sir.
알겠습니다, 대령님
출동합니다
Psst!
- [ Whispering ] Rover! Spotty!
- Hmm. What?
점박아!
뭐야?
네가 도둑맞은 15마리의
강아지 중 하나니?
Are you one of
the 15 stolen puppies?
We're not stolen.
We're bought and paid for.
아니요, 우리는 팔려 왔어요
There's 99 of us
all together.
모두 99마리나 돼요
Ninety-nine!
99마리?
How 'bout that bunch
of little ones?
혹시 쟤들이 아닐까요?
목걸이에 이름이 있어요
They have names and colors.
They're not from the pet shops.
팔려온 게 아니란 얘기죠
15마리니?
- Fifteen of 'em?
- We never counted them.
세어보진 않았어요
TV 앞에 있는 애들이에요
They're over there
by the tv.
- I'd better count 'em.
- Watch out for the baduns.
세어봐야겠다
악당들 조심하세요
Baduns?
악당들?
Those two blokes,
Horace and Jasper.
호레스와 재스퍼요
정말 나쁜 사람들이에요
They're mean ones,
they are.
♪♪ [ TV ]
Hey, look, Horace!
호레스, 내가 명중시킬 테니
보고 있어
Watch me pot His Lordship
smack on the conk.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
How's that for callin' 'em, eh?
형님 솜씨가 어때?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
[ Whispering ]
One... two...
하나, 둘, 셋...
다섯, 여섯...
- three, four, five, six--
- Hey, Jasper.
재스퍼
[ Mumbling ]
Give us a swig,
한 모금만 주라
딱 한 모금만
- just a short one.
- Now, Horace,
너 같은 촌놈에게
이런 고급술은 안 어울려
this hogwash ain't fit
for a fancy bloke like yourself.
Besides, you'd get crumbs in it,
you cabbage head!
입이 부르틀걸
All right.
그래, 다 먹어라
그러면 기분 퍽도 좋겠다
Guzzle the whole works. I hope it
gives you colly wobbles, that's what.
Hey, Jasper.
Did you--
재스퍼, 혹시 너...
Six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven--
여섯, 일곱, 여덟...
Hey, get down, you runt!
And stay down!
꼬맹아!
앉아있지 못해!
[ Yipping ]
Go on, get out of here...
까불면 다른 쪽 눈도
점박이를 만들어 놓겠어
or I'll black
your other peeper.
Where was l?
Nine--
어디까지 세었더라
9에 3이 더 있고...
Nine... three more.
Twelve and... one, two, three.
That's fifteen!
열둘에 그걸 더하면...
15마리다!
They're the ones!
저 애들이 틀림없어
- [ Screeching ]
- Blimey!
이런 재수없게...
- [ Barking ]
- What the--
Horace, look what we got!
A tabby cat!
호레스, 손님이 왔어
도둑고양이야
[ Yipping ]
Ha-ha-ha!
Ho-ho-ho!
How'd you like
a tabby cat stew?
너 고양이 좋아하냐?
고양이 요리는 어때?
Or a cat casserole?
A la mode!
맛있겠지?
[ Howling ]
[ Chiming ]
[ Howling And Barking ]
- What is it, Pongo? What is it?
- It's the great dane.
뭐예요, 퐁고?
대니의 연락이야
전해줄 소식이 있대
장미 언덕으로 나오라는데
He has news for us.
He'll meet us at Primrose Hill.
어떻게 나가죠?
- How'll we get out?
- The back bedroom window.
침실 뒤 창문으로 나가면 돼
항상 약간씩 열려있거든
It's always open
a wee bit. C'mon.
- Woof! Woof!
- [ Barking ]
Pongos, you've made it.
Good.
빨리 와줬군, 퐁고
- What's the word? What's the news?
- Have they found our puppies?
무슨 소식이죠?
아가들을 찾았나요?
They've been located
somewhere north of here...
서포크 북쪽 어딘가에
있다는군
- in Suffolk.
- Oh, thank heaven.
다행이에요
- Can you leave tonight?
- We can leave right away.
-오늘밤 떠날 수 있나?
-그럼요
지금 당장이요
좋아, 캠던 도로까지 가서
길을 가르쳐 주겠네
I'll go along as far as Camden Road
and give you instructions.
[ Dane ] When you reach
Withermarsh, contact old Towser.
위서마시에 가거든
타우저를 찾아가게
대령님이 크루엘라의 집으로
안내해 주실걸세
He'll direct you to the Colonel
and the Colonel will take you...
to your puppies
at the de Vil place.
크루엘라요?
- De Vil!
- The de Vil place!
크루엘라네 집이요?
Oh, Pongo,
it was her!
역시 그 여자였어요
아는 개인가?
- Oh, someone you know?
- There's no time to explain.
설명드릴 시간이 없습니다
I hope we're
not too late.
늦지나 않았을지...
Good luck, Pongo.
행운을 비네, 퐁고
길을 잃으면 다시
비상 경보를 보내게!
If you lose your way,
contact the barking chain.
모두 대기시켜 놓았네!
They'll be
standing by!
[ Honking ]
Any news, Colonel?
소식 있습니까, 대령님?
Not a blasted thing.
감감 무소식이야
길을 잃었거나 잡혔거나...
They're lost or captured,
or something or other.
- Who knows what.
- Colonel, here comes a car.
대령님, 저기 차가 옵니다
Come now, Tibs.
Don't be ridiculous.
쓸데없는 소리 마
퐁고가 차를 타고 올 리 없잖아
- They wouldn't be driving.
- Y es, I know, sir.
그게 아니에요
유령의 집을 향해 가는데요
But it's heading
for Hell Hall.
It-- It's stopping
at the gate!
대문에 멈췄어요
It is?
그래?
Blast it all!
Better see what's up.
무슨 일인지 보고오자
야옹이 상사, 출동이다!
- On the double, man. On the double!
- Y es, sir.
알겠습니다!
Take over, Captain.
이곳을 맡기겠다
Righto, sir.
알겠습니다
[ TV Quiz Master ] I'm sorry,
Mr. Simpkins. The answer is no, no, no.
죄송합니다, 심킨 씨
대답은 '아니오'입니다
여섯 번 했으니까
네 번 남았군요
Six down, four to go.
I've got no time to argue.
It's got to be done tonight.
실랑이할 시간 없어
오늘밤 안에 일을 끝내
It must be a yes
or no question.
대답은 '네, 아니오'로만
할 수 있습니다
Do you understand?
Tonight!
알아들었나?
오늘밤이야!
[ Horace ]
But they ain't big enough.
하지만 너무 어려요
다 벗겨봐야 코트 여섯 벌도
만들기 힘들걸요
You couldn't get half a dozen coats
out of the whole caboodle.
다 벗겨봐야 코트 여섯 벌도
만들기 힘들걸요
You couldn't get half a dozen coats
out of the whole caboodle.
개가죽 코트?
Coats!
Dog-skin coats?
그럼 여섯 벌만 만들어
더 기다릴 수 없어
We'll settle for half a dozen!
We can't wait.
The police are everywhere.
I want the job done tonight!
경찰이 사방에 깔렸어
오늘밤에 끝내야 해
How're we gonna do it?
어떻게 벗기죠?
Any way you like.
Poison them, drown them.
독을 먹이든 익사를 시키든
마음대로 해
Bash them in the head.
You got any chloroform?
마취제는 있나?
- Not a drop.
- And no ether, "ee-ther."
하나도 없어요
이것도 떨어...
떨어 졌어요
"Eye-ther"!
말 똑바로 해
I don't care how you kill the little
beasts, but do it... and do it now!
어떻게 죽이든 상관없으니까
일만 끝내, 당장!
Aw, please, miss.
Have pity.
사람이 인정이 있어야죠
Can't we see the rest
of the show first?
보던 프로는
마저 보게 해주세요
범죄 맞추기 프로거든요
[ Horace ] We want to see
"What's My Crime?"
[ Explosion ]
Listen, you idiots!
내 말 잘 들어, 이 멍청아
I'll be back in the morning.
The job better be done...
내일 아침에 올 테니까
일을 끝내놓도록 해
아니면
경찰에 신고할거야!
or I'll--
I'll call the police!
Do you understand?
알아듣겠나?
I think she means it.
진심인 것 같아, 재스퍼
Ah...
We'll get on with it...
이 프로만 끝나면
즉시 시작하자구
as soon as
the show's over.
써 주시겠습니까?
Will you please
sign in, sir?
얘들아, 살고 싶으면
여길 빠져나가야 해
You'd better get out of here
if you want to save your skins.
어떻게요?
- But how?
- Shh.
벽에 구멍이 있어
저쪽 문 있는 곳이야
There's a hole in the wall
there by the door.
C'mon, shake a leg.
어서 날 따라와
어서!
Psst.
Kids, follow me.
[ Horace ] Hey, Jasper, look!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
봐!
그 멍청이가 나왔어
It's old Meathead.
Yeah, what do you know...
old Meathead Fauncewater.
그래, 정말 그놈일세
C'mon,
don't crowd.
순서대로 나가
한번에 한 명씩
One at a time.
One at a time!
For our last contestant,
마지막 출연자는
폰스워터 씨 입니다
meet Mr. Percival Fauncewater.
If the panel fails to guess your
unusual crime in ten questions,
만약 당신이 저지른 범죄를
10번만에 맞추지 못하면
you will receive two weeks vacation
at a seaside resort,
2주간 휴가를 가게 됩니다
all expenses paid.
모든 경비는
우리가 대고 말이죠
[ Quiz Master ] That is, after
you've paid your debt to society.
물론 복역을 마친 후가
되겠지만요
Who will take the first
question? Inspector?
누가 제일 먼저 질문을
하시겠습니까? 형사님?
당신이 저지른 범죄는
절도죄에 해당합니까?
Could your crime
be classified as larceny?
- A theft, burglary?
- Straighten out!
도둑질이나 강도 같은 것
말입니다
Form a queue... along the wall.
Snap it up.
벽 옆으로 한줄로 서!
어서 빨리!
[ Quiz Master ] Mr. Fauncewater
is a burglar by trade,
폰스워터 씨가
강도 전문인 건 사실이지만
but in this case,
his crime was not burglary.
이번 죄목은 다릅니다
죄송합니다
대답은 '아니오'입니다
- The answer is no.
- [ Laughing ]
One down, nine to go.
Miss Birdwell?
하나 틀렸고 9개 남았군요
버드웰 씨?
If your crime
wasn't robbery, did you--
절도가 아니라면 혹시...
Oh, dear,
what I mean is--
폭력과 관련된 범죄가
아닐까요?
Do something of
a violent nature, that is--
시간이 없습니다, 버드웰 양
Come, Miss Birdwell,
we're running short of time.
[ Miss Birdwell ] So sorry.
알겠어요
혹시 누군가를 죽였나요?
- Did you do someone in?
- Oh!
대답은 '아니오'입니다
[ Quiz Master ] I'm sorry.
The answer is no.
Two down,
eight to go.
2개 틀렸으니 8개 남았군요
- Mr. Simpkins?
- Psst.
-심킨 씨
-네
살인도 아니라면...
Hey, kid, let's go.
얘야, 가자!
[ Mr. Simpkins ] Could it be
a violation of a city ordinance?
무슨 법을 어긴 건
아닌가요?
No.
아닙니다
Hey, get out of the way,
you little runt!
비켜, 이 콩알아
[ Quiz Master ] Three down,
seven to go. Inspector?
3개 틀리고 7개 남았네요
[ lnspector ] Very confusing,
I must say.
상당히 까다롭군요
Surely,
this crime could--
그렇다면 이 범죄는...
- [ Buzzer ]
- I'm terribly sorry.
죄송합니다
시간이 다 됐습니다
-We've run out of time.
-[ Horace ] Ain't that always the way!
항상 저런 식이라니까
Would it be possible for
Mr. Fauncewater to come back next week?
폰스워터 씨, 다음주에
다시 나와줄 수 있을까요?
그래야 게임을 끝낼 수 있죠
Then we could finish
our little game.
Good night, audience.
See you next week at this same time...
안녕히 계십시오
다음주 같은 시간
'범죄 찾기'에서 뵙겠습니다
on "What's My Crime?"
Ah, oh well.
C'mon, Horace.
Let's get on with it.
슬슬 시작할까
I'll pop 'em on the head,
you do the skinnin'.
내가 머리를 비틀 테니까
네가 가죽을 벗겨
싫어, 재스퍼
내가 죽이고 네가 벗겨
No you don't, Jasper!
I'll pop 'em off and
you do the skinnin'.
Horace, look!
호레스, 저기 좀 봐!
전부 사라졌어
They're gone.
They flew the coop...
저 개구멍으로 도망쳤어
right out through this hole.
Here, grab a torch.
가자! 하나라도 놓치면
내가 성을 갈아버릴 테다
We'll run 'em down before
you can say "Bob's your uncle."
[ Whimpering ]
저기 간다! 계단 쪽이야!
There they go, Horace,
up the stairs.
[ Whistling ]
Here puppies.
착하지, 아가야
[ Whistling ]
Here, puppies!
C'mon now.
어서 와라, 강아지야
숨으면 아저씨가 섭섭하지
Don't go hiding from
ol' Uncle Jasper.
I ain't gonna hurt ya.
해치지 않을게
I thought we was
gonna pop 'em off.
죽여서 가죽을 벗길 거면서?
Shut up.
Take a squint in there.
시끄러워!
그쪽을 뒤져, 난 다른 방을 볼게
I'll check these
other two rooms.
[ Whistling ]
Here, puppies.
나와라, 아가야
Come on out.
Come out wherever you are.
어서 나와라
[ Screeching ]
Horace! Oh!
도둑고양이가
이놈들 대장이야!
[ Jasper ] It's that mangy tabby cat.
He's the ringleader.
Head 'em off.
Head 'em--
머리를 쳐버려, 호레스
[ Yipping ]
You bungling blockhead!
앞 좀 잘 보고 다녀!
Back here!
여기 숨어
Shh.
Here they come.
저기 온다
Double-crossin' little twerps,
pullin' a snitch on us!
은혜도 모르는 것들 같으니
먹여주고 재워줬더니
고마운 줄 모르고 도망 가?
After we took care of 'em.
There's gratitude for you.
나쁜 녀석들이야
It ain't fair, Jasper.
- [ Whining ]
- Horace, there they go!
호레스, 저기 있다!
Sergeant?
I say, Sergeant.
이봐, 상사!
No time to explain.
Busy, sir.
나중에 설명 드리죠
너무 바쁩니다
문을 닫아!
Shut that door!
We'll close in on 'em.
Enough of this "Ring Around the Rosy."
우선 가두고
본 떼를 보여주는 거야
Oh, Pongo,
I'm afraid we're lost.
퐁고, 길을 잃은 것 같아요
거의 다 왔을 텐데
It can't be far.
[ Barking ]
By Jove!
It can't be the Pongos.
저건 퐁고 소리 같은데?
[ Barking ]
Grrr...
[ Howling ]
It's the Colonel.
This way.
대령님이다, 이쪽이야
[ Barking And Howling ]
Colonel?
Are you the Colonel?
대령님이십니까?
Oh, Pingo!
Uh-- Uh-- Pongo?
핑고, 자넨가?
아니, 퐁고였지
Our puppies,
are they all right?
우리 애들은요?
전부 무사한가요?
No time to explain.
There's trouble.
설명할 시간이 없다
상황이 급해
난리가 났어, 어서 가지
A big hullabaloo.
Come along!
Follow me!
날 따라와라!
Ah, ha-ha-ha!
Now we've got 'em, Horace.
They've run out of room.
너희는 끝났다
독 안에 든 쥐야
이건 또 뭐야?
점박이 하이에나인가?
What have we got here?
A couple of spotted hyenas?
C'mon, Horace.
Give 'em what for.
호레스, 네가 맡아
내가 있으니까
뒤는 걱정 말고
I'm right
behind ya, lad.
Uh... oh!
You clumsy clod!
누구를 치는 거야?
I'll knock the spots off you.
Let go!
실수로 널 친 거란다
한 번만 봐줘!
떨어지지 못해?
Let go!
[ Barking ]
Well, by George!
너 이제 혼났다
[ Whimpering ]
You mangy mongrel!
이런 왕빈대 같은 개자식!
I'll knock your
blinkin' block off.
너도 맛 좀 봐라
Yeow!
절대 놓치지 마라!
항복을 받아야 한다!
Blast 'em, Tibs.
Give 'em what for.
No, Colonel.
Retreat, retreat!
대령님!
후퇴해야 해요
Yes. Yes, of course.
Retreat!
후퇴?
그래, 후퇴도 좋지
Retreat, on the double!
즉각 후퇴하라!
Help, Jasper!
Get me out of here!
재스퍼, 나 좀 살려 줘
놈들이 치사하게 나오는데
Horace, they're
fighting dirty!
Oh, oh, oh!
Jasper!
재스퍼!
호레스!
Horace!
[ Groaning ]
C'mon, Perdy.
Let's go.
가자, 퍼디
I'll skin every one
of them spotted hyenas...
내 목숨을 걸고라도 저놈의
하이에나를 없애고 말겠다!
if it's
the last thing I do.
[ Puppies ]
Dad! Mother!
아빠! 엄마!
- I missed you, Mommy.
- Here we are, Mommy.
엄마, 엄마
너무 보고 싶었어요
Oh, my darlings...
my darlings!
우리 아가들...
어떻게 찾으셨어요?
- How'd you find us?
- Lucky, Patch, Pepper!
럭키, 패치, 페퍼
[ Laughing ]
Oh, Daddy.
- And Rolly, you rascal!
- Did you bring me anything to eat?
그리고 롤리, 장난꾸러기
먹을 거 갖고 왔어요?
Everybody here?
All 15?
모두 있는 거냐?
15명 모두?
Twice that many, Dad.
Now there's 99 of us!
두 배는 더 많아요
전부 99마리예요
What?
Nine-- 99?
99마리나?
모두 어디서 온 거냐?
[ Pongo ] Where did they
all come from?
이렇게 많은 강아지로
뭘 하려고 했을까요?
[ Perdy ] What would she want
with so many?
She's gonna make
coats out of us.
우리를 갖고
코트를 만든대요
- She couldn't!
- That's right, dog-skin coats.
설마!
맞습니다
개가죽 코트죠
Oh, dog-skin coats!
Come now, Tibs!
개가죽 코트라
세상에 그런 말을...
But it's true, sir.
사실인 걸요
Horace and Jasper were gonna
pop us off and... skin us!
호레스와 재스퍼가 우리를
죽이고 가죽을 벗긴댔어요
She's a devil, a witch!
What'll we do?
악마 같은 여자!
이 일을 어떡하죠?
We have to get back
to London somehow.
어떻게든
런던으로 돌아 가야해
다른 애들은요?
그 애들은 어떡해요?
What about the others?
What'll they do?
Perdy, we'll take them
home with us... all of them.
퍼디, 모두 함께 가는 거야
Our pets would
never turn them out.
로저는 거절할 사람이 아니야
Colonel, sir,
lights on the road.
대령님, 차가 오는데요
트럭에 이쪽으로 옵니다
It's a truck
headin' this way.
[ Tibs ] It's the baduns,
Horace and Jasper.
호레스와 재스퍼가
발자국을 따라 온 거예요
They're following
our tracks.
We've got 'em
outnumbered, Tibs.
수적으로 우리가 우세해
내가 신호하면 모두 공격한다
When I give the signal,
we'll attack.
Sir, I'm afraid that
would be disastrous.
대령님, 숫자는 많지만
전부 강아지인데요
Ahem!
Oh, think so?
그런가?
맞습니다, 달아나야 해요
We'd better
run for it.
Out the back,
across the pasture.
뒤로 가서
풀밭을 가로질러 가요
감사합니다, 상사님
대령님과 소대장님도요
Thank you sergeant,
Colonel, Captain.
- Bless you all.
- How can we ever repay you?
-축복 받으실 거예요
-이 은혜를 어떻게 갚죠?
Ahem! Nothing at all.
All in the line of duty.
천만의 말씀
군인이라면 당연하죠
맞습니다, 보통이죠
That's right, sir...
routine.
Better be off.
Here they come.
그만 떠나죠, 놈들이 와요
다들 서두르자
C'mon, kids, hurry.
행운을 빕니다, 퐁고
- Good luck, Pongos.
- [ Colonel ] And never fear.
우리가 끝까지 저들을 물고
늘어질 테니까 걱정 말게나!
We'll hold them off
'til the bitter end.
[ Neighing ]
Now, what's this?
이건 또 뭐야?
Out of my way,
you barkin' haystack.
당장 꺼지지 못해?
멍청한 멍멍아
Or I'll knock your
blinkin' block off!
[ Barking And Growling ]
They ain't in here.
여긴 없는데, 재스퍼
[ Jasper ] They're hiding
in the hay.
건초더미 안에 숨었을 거야
Give me a match.
We'll burn 'em out.
성냥 줘봐
전부 태워 버리게
준비 됐죠?
Ready, Captain.
Aim,
조준!
fire one.
발사!
Fire two.
2탄 발사!
Hey, there they go,
the little sneaks.
얄미운 것들이 저기 간다
C'mon, back to the truck.
We'll head 'em off in half a mile.
어서 트럭에 타
조금만 가면 잡을 수 있어
They gotta be around
here somewhere.
이 근처에 있을 텐데
- I've been thinkin'.
- Now, Horace.
재스퍼, 생각해봤는데...
됐어, 호레스
What if they went down
the froze-up creek...
발자국을 남기지 않으려고
얼음 위로 도망간 게 아닐까?
so's not to leave
their tracks?
Horace, you idiot!
호레스
이런 바보
개들은 그렇게 똑똑하지 못해
- Dogs ain't that smart.
- [ Sighs ]
[ Truck Engine ]
All clear, Perdy.
됐어, 퍼디
이제 안전해
- All clear.
- We gave 'em the slip!
Didn't we, Dad?
우리한테 속았어
그렇죠, 아빠?
They didn't even
see us, Patch!
여기 있을 줄
꿈에도 몰랐을걸
[ Perdy ] Shh, children.
Children, shh.
조용히 해라
My feet are slippery.
너무 미끄러워요
I wish we could
walk on the snow.
눈 위로 가면 좋은데
그럼 발자국이 남잖니
No, son, we can't
leave tracks.
[ Honking, Tires Screeching ]
Well, any sign
of them?
찾아냈나?
Not so much as
one bloomin' footprint.
강아지 발자국이
하나도 없어요
이 근처를 이 잡듯 샅샅이
뒤졌는데도 없네요
And we've been up and down
every road in the county.
얼어죽겠어요
우리는 포기할래요
- We're froze stiff. We're givin' up.
- Oh, no, you don't!
누구 맘대로?
We'll find the little mongrels
if it takes 'til next Christmas.
무슨 수를 쓰든
놈들을 찾아야 해
Now get going!
Watch your driving!
어서 가라!
그리고 운전 좀 똑바로 해
경찰에 잡혀가고 싶어?
Do you wanna get
nabbed by the police?
[ Engine Revving ]
Ninety-three,
93, 94, 95, 96...
ninety-four,
ninety-five, ninety-six,
ninety-seven,
97, 98...
ninety-eight...
럭키야
Oh, Lucky!
C'mon, Lucky boy.
We can't give up now.
힘내라, 럭키야
여기서 포기하면 안돼
배고프고 지쳤어요
꼬리도 얼고
I'm tired and I'm hungry
and my tail's froze...
코도 얼고
귀도 얼고
and my nose is froze
and my ears are froze.
발가락도 얼었어요
- And my toes are froze.
- [ Barking ]
Pongo!
퐁고!
Pongo! Pongo!
We'd just about lost hope.
We have shelter for you...
포기하려던 참이었네
쉴 곳을 마련했어
at the dairy barn
across the road.
길 건너에 있는 목장이야
Oh, thank goodness.
정말 고마워요
퍼디!
Perdy! Perdy!
This way, Perdy.
길 건너에 목장이 있대
- The dairy barn across the road.
- C'mon, kids.
가자, 얘들아
It's not far.
C'mon, this way.
그리 멀지 않아, 이쪽이야
콜리 아저씨를 따라가라
[ Pongo ] Follow the collie.
Just look, Queenie.
퀴니, 이렇게 많은 강아지
본 적 있어?
- Have you ever seen so many puppies?
- Aren't they adorable!
귀엽기도 해라
- Perfectly darling.
- The poor dears.
깨물어주고 싶어
가엾은 것 같으니
얼마나 춥고 배고팠을까
녹초가 다 됐네
They're completely worn out
and half frozen!
- They all here, Pongo?
- Yes, dear. All 99 accounted for.
전부 들어 왔어요?
그래, 99마리 전부 무사해
The famous Pongos.
We were so worried about you.
그 유명한 퐁고 씨군요
걱정 많이 했어요
Been trying to reach you.
Afraid you'd been captured.
한참 기다려도 안 오길래
잡힌 줄 알았네
How did you make it
all this way?
어떻게 여기까지
올 수 있었죠?
- And in such dreadful weather.
- With all those little ones.
이런 추운 날씨에 말이죠
저런 꼬맹이들을 데리고요
배고파, 엄마
배가 고파요
I'm hungry, Mother.
I'm hungry.
- I'm hungry too.
- Mother, we're hungry.
나도 배고파요, 엄마
우리 모두 배고파요
- We're all hungry.
- I'm sorry, children.
미안하구나, 얘들아
Do they like warm milk?
It's fresh.
애들이 우유 좋아해요?
내 우유는 신선한데
어디요? 어디 있는데요?
- Where is it?
- Where is the milk?
우유가 어디 있죠?
와서 먹으렴, 얘들아
Come and get it, kids.
It's on the house.
이쪽이다, 얘들아
돌아서 와야지
This way, children.
Around this way.
[ Perdy ] Don't crowd.
You'll have to take turns.
밀지 말고
돌아가면서 먹어
롤리, 차례대로 해야지
[ Perdy ] Rolly, wait your turn, dear.
Don't worry, kids.
There's plenty for all.
걱정 말아라
우유는 충분히 있단다
Ooh!
The little darlings.
귀여운 것들
Pongo, a few scraps
I saved...
둘 먹을 것도 준비했어
- for you and the missus.
- Oh, thank you.
고맙습니다
많지는 않지만 딘스포드에
갈 때까지 버틸 수 있을 거야
It's not much, but it might
hold you as far as Dinsford.
Huh?
Dinsford?
딘스포드요?
There's a Labrador there.
그곳에 사냥개가 있어
주인이 가게를 하지
- His pet is a grocer.
- Oh, l-- I'm sorry.
정말 미안해요
괜찮아, 푹 쉬도록 하게
내가 경비를 서겠네
Quite all right.
Get some rest and don't worry.
I'll be standing watch.
I don't know what
we'd have done if--
어떻게 인사를 해야 할지...
- We're honored to be of service.
- We're sorry we can't do more.
아니에요
우리가 흐뭇한 걸요
더 도와주지 못해서
안타까워요
이렇게 귀여운 강아지를
해치려 들다니...
[ Duchess ] Anyone who would think
of hurting these puppies--
- Shh! Duchess!
- They're so dear.
조용히 해!
너무 귀여워
여기서 함께 살면 얼마나 좋을까
I wish they could stay
with us for always.
프린세스, 조용히 해
자게 좀 내버려 둬
[ Queenie ] Princess, shh.
Quiet, everyone.
Let them sleep,
the poor things.
너무 지쳐있어
They're so exhausted and they
still have such a long way to go.
갈 길이 먼데 어쩌나
[ Honking ]
Hurry, kids. Hurry!
서둘러라, 얘들아!
[ Honking ]
[ Screeching ]
Well now,
what have we here?
이게 무슨 자국이지?
Well... so they thought
they could outwit Cruella.
날 속일 수 있다고
생각했다 이거지?
- Ha-ha-ha-ha!
- [ Honking ]
재스퍼! 호레스!
Jasper!
Horace!
Here's their tracks
heading for the village.
놈들이
마을을 향해 가고 있어
Blimey!
It's them, all right.
놈들이 맞군요
너희는 옆길로 가라
난 큰길로 갈 테니
Work your way south on the side roads.
I'll take the main road.
[ Cruella ]
See you in Dinsford!
딘스포드에서 만나자!
[ Barking ]
"딘스포드"
Pongo, I've got
a ride home for you.
퐁고, 집까지 갈 교통편을
마련해 놨어
A ride home?
Perdy, did you hear that?
교통편?
당신도 들었어?
- For all of us?
- You mean we don't have to
walk anymore?
우리 전부 다요?
그럼 걷지 않아도 되나요?
잘하면 가능하지
어서 서둘러야 해
If we can manage it.
We'd better hurry.
차를 타고 갈 수 있단다
어서, 얘들아
We've got a ride home!
C'mon, children.
See the van
down the street?
저기 트럭 보이지?
수리가
끝나면 런던으로 떠날 거야
[ Labrador ] It's going to London
as soon as the engine's repaired.
모두 다 충분히 탈 수 있어
And there's room
for all of you.
퐁고, 크루엘라예요
[ Perdy ]
Pongo, there's Cruella.
Yes...
그래
재스퍼와 호레스도 있군
and Jasper and Horace.
퐁고, 트럭까지 어떻게 가죠?
- How will we get to the van?
- I don't know, Perdy.
나도 모르겠어
- But somehow we've got to.
- Mother, Dad,
하지만 어떻게든 가야해
엄마, 아빠
패치가 벽난로 속으로 밀어요
- Patch pushed me in the fireplace.
- Lucky pushed me first.
럭키가 먼저 그랬어요
-안 그랬어
-그랬어!
- Did not. Did not.
- Did too. Did too.
안 그랬어
Did not!
싸우지 말아라
- Please, children, don't quarrel.
- Say...
퍼디, 좋은 생각이 났어
Perdy, I've got an idea.
Pongo,
무슨 짓이에요?
- what on earth--
- Look, I'm a Labrador!
봐, 사냥개 같지?
We'll all roll in soot.
We'll be Labradors.
모두 석탄가루에서 뒹굴면
아무도 몰라 볼 거야
Say, that is an idea!
좋은 생각이야
C'mon, kids!
Roll in the soot.
얘들아, 어서 뒹굴어라
몸을 더럽히라고요?
You mean, you want
us to get dirty?
너도 들었지?
Did you hear that, Freckles?
Dad wants us to get dirty.
아빠가 몸을 더럽히래
- Mother, should we?
- Do as your father says.
엄마, 해도 돼요?
아빠 말씀대로 하거라
- This'll be fun.
- I always wanted to get good and dirty.
신난다!
언젠가는 이래보고 싶었어
[ Giggling ]
[ Pongo ] That's the stuff.
The blacker the better.
까맣게 될수록 좋아
-전 다 됐어요
-저두요
- I'm ready.
- Me too.
저 어때요?
- How's this, Dad?
- Wait. That's enough.
Not too many at a time.
한번에 너무 많이 나가면 안돼
Uh-oh. Rolly, hold on.
You're only half done.
롤리, 잠깐만
넌 반밖에 안됐구나
Now, stay right with me.
이제 날 따라오도록 해라
We're gonna fool
the ol' mad lady.
그 나쁜 여자가 약 오르겠다
Pongo...
여보
겁나요
I'm so afraid.
Jasper, do you suppose
they disguised themselves?
재스퍼
놈들이 변장을 한 게 아닐까?
Say now, Horace.
That's just what they did.
변장이랄 게 어디 있냐?
Dogs is always paintin'
themselves black!
잠시만 놔둬도
더러워지는 게 개야
이런 바보야!
You idiot!
Well, so far
so good.
지금까지는 성공이야, 퍼디
당신도 변장해
C'mon, Perdy.
Better get on your makeup.
그 다음에 내가 할게
I'll go ahead
with the next bunch.
[ Cruella ]
Jasper! Horace!
재스퍼, 호레스!
- Well?
- Be reasonable, miss.
찾았나?
제발 다그치지 좀 말아요
[ Horace ] We're froze to our bones.
뼛속까지 얼었어요
We've been out all night
and all day, with nothin' to eat.
하루 종일 아무 것도
못 먹었다구요
They're somewhere in this village,
and we're going to find them.
이 마을 어딘가에 있어
꼭 찾아야 해
어서 움직여!
Now get going!
우리를 봤을까요?
- Do you think they've seen us?
- [ Engine ]
아니, 하지만 시간이
별로 없어
No, but we're
running out of time.
다시 해봐
Try 'er again, mate.
Hurry, Perdy.
The van's about to leave.
빨리 해, 퍼디
차가 떠나려고 해
Better hurry.
서둘러
I'll get the rest.
나머지도 데려올게
이 정도면
런던까지 갈 수 있을 거야
That ought to do.
She'll get you back to London.
Better get aboard, miss.
어서 타요, 부인
Hey, Jasper.
이봐, 재스퍼
[ Whimpering ]
C'mon, Horace.
들어가자, 호레스
빨리 가자!
Hurry, kids!
먼저 뛰어가
C'mon, kids.
Run on ahead.
우리를 쳐다봐요, 아빠
- She's watching us, Dad.
- Keep going.
계속 가라, 계속
It can't be!
이럴 수가!
말도 안돼!
It's impossible!
어서 뛰어!
[ Labrador ] Run for it!
- Jasper! Horace!
- [ Honking ]
재스퍼!
호레스!
Jasper!
재스퍼!
[ Cruella ] There they go...
in the van.
저기 트럭에 타고있어
After them! After them!
놈들을 쫓아라!
[ Barking And Growling ]
Pongo!
There she is... Cruella.
퐁고!
그 여자가 쫓아와요
Hey, lady,
이봐 여자씨!
도대체 무슨 짓이야?
what in thunder
are you tryin' to do?
Crazy woman driver!
미친 여자 같으니!
[ Engine Revving ]
- Pongo, look!
- Jasper!
퐁고, 봐요!
재스퍼!
이제 혼 좀 나봐라
저 차 옆구리를 받아서
Ain't nothin' to it.
I'll give him a nudge
and shove him in the dirt.
밀어버릴 테다!
Perdy, watch out!
퍼디, 조심해!
- Jasper!
- Horace!
재스퍼!
호레스!
You idiots!
멍청한 것들!
You fools!
한심한 것들아!
네놈들 때문에 난 망했다
[ Sobbing ]
You imbeciles!
좀 닥치시요
- Ah, shut up!
- [ Sobbing ]
[ Radio ]
♪ You've seen her kind of eyes ♪
'동굴속에서 보는
그런 눈을 본 적 있지'
♪ Watchin' you from underneath a rock ♪
♪ Cruella de Vil ♪
'크루엘라 드빌...'
♪ Cruella de-- ♪
Roger, after all,
that's your first big hit.
당신의 첫 히트곡이군요
It's made more money
than we ever dreamed of.
덕분에 돈도 많이 벌었구요
Yes, I know.
그래...
퐁고와 퍼디가 도망갔다는 게
믿어지지 않아
I still can't believe...
that Pongo and Perdy
would run away.
Here's a bit of
Christmas cheer for you,
크리스마스 기분 좀 내시라고
가져왔어요
즐거울 일도 없지만요
If there's anything
to be cheerful about.
그 귀여운것들...
Oh, those dear
little things.
Sometimes at night
I can hear them barking,
어떨 때는 밖에서
애들 짖는 소리가 들려요
- [ Barking ]
- but it always turns out I'm dreaming.
나가보면 아무도 없곤 하죠
[ Barking ]
[ Anita ] Roger, what on earth--
로저, 무슨 일이죠?
웬 사냥개들이야?
[ Roger ] They're labradors.
검댕이 묻어서 그래요
No, no.
They're covered with soot.
봐요, 럭키잖아요
Look, here's Lucky!
Pongo, boy,
is that you?
퐁고, 네가 맞니?
Oh, Pongo, Pongo!
Ho-ho, it's Pongo!
퐁고야!
And Perdy,
my darling.
퍼디, 무사했구나
패치, 롤리, 페니, 프레클
And Patch, and Rolly,
and Penny, and Freckles.
모두 무사해요
They're all here,
the little dears.
이건 기적이야
- It's a miracle!
- What a wonderful Christmas present!
이보다 기쁜 선물은 없어요
And look...
there's a whole lot more!
봐요!
밖에도 더 있어요
- Look, Anita, puppies everywhere.
- There must be 100!
여보, 사방이 강아지 천지야
백 마리는 되겠어요
하나, 둘, 셋, 넷...
여덟...
One, two, three and
four... is seven.
Two, four, six, and three
is nine, plus two is eleven.
둘, 넷, 여섯...
아홉에 둘이니 열 하나
이쪽은 36마리예요
- 36 over here.
- 36 and 11, that's 47!
36에 11이면 47
이쪽은 18마리예요
- Eighteen, Roger.
- That's 65!
그럼 65마리네
Ten, eleven,
twelve, thirteen!
10, 11, 12,
13!
잠깐만요
6마리 더요
- Wait... six more.
- Let's see, that's 84.
그럼 84마리에 15를 더하고
둘을 더하면...
And fifteen plus two...
a hundred and one!
101마리야!
A hundred and one?
Where did they come from?
101마리요?
모두 어디서 온 거죠?
Oh, Pongo,
you old rascal!
퐁고, 엉뚱한 녀석 같으니
- What'll we do with them?
- We'll keep 'em.
다 어떡하죠?
길러야지
이 집에서요?
- In this little house?
- We'll buy a big place in the country.
시골에 큰 집을 사는 거야
We'll have a plantation--
a dalmatian plantation.
개 농장을 만들지 뭐
달마시안 개 농장 말야!
정말 좋은 생각이네요!
Roger, that's truly
an inspiration.
굉장할 거예요
It'll be a sensation!
We'll have
a dalmatian plantation.
우린 달마시안 농장을 할 거야
멋진 달마시안 농장이
될 거야
A dalmatian plantation,
I say.
'우리는 달마시안 농장을
할 거예요'
♪ We'll have a dalmatian plantation ♪
- ♪ Where our population can roam ♪
- I'm hungry.
배고파요, 엄마
'참사랑이 넘치는
달마시안 농장이죠'
♪ Our whole aggregation
will love our plantation home ♪
♪ Woo-woo-woo-woo ♪
♪ Oo-oo-oo ♪
♪ ♪ [ Yipping ]
♪ Dalmatian plantation home ♪ ♪
'점박이 강아지
달마시안 농장이에요'
[ Barking And Yipping ]